Just where do you think you're running off to, Beta?
What was that?
Icarus, what's the matter?
Nothing.
Gamma!
You got it. We're the Angeloid Interceptors. Type Gamma and Type Harpy.
It's the Uranus Queen Swanson. We're here to take the bitch down.
Don't you worry about a thing. You see, Master asked us to do this.
I'll bet you didn't know he's been watching over you this entire time.
Actually, he's been quite worried about you.
He's worried about me?
Well, he did tell you to take on the Uranus Queen by yourself.
And that's a hell of a tall order for anyone, even one of us.
When he realized you might get hurt attempting it, he acted quickly to mount a rescue.
He sent us here to bring you home as soon as possible.
Sounds like Master's pretty lonely without you up there with him, Beta.
Master's worried about me. And he's actually lonely without me, too. I never expected that.
As much as she enjoys hanging around those insects, this must be torturing her.
She'll destroy the Uranus Queen, kill the humans, and then return to me, filled with joy.
Certain I'm going to applaud what a good job she did.
And that's the moment I'll tell the wretched thing.
It's time to send your ass to the scrapyard.
I can't wait to see the horrified face she makes when I drop that bomb on her.
There is no more time.
Hear me. You must save the angel, please.
She is being held by the sky.
That same weird-ass dream again.
Are you finally waking up, Master?
Yeah. Where's Nymph?
Well, she's...
What? Are you serious? Nymph pulled another disappearing act?
Correct. This is becoming something of a pattern.
She's making me crazy. What's her deal?
Like Icarus said, she's always taking off.
Come on, you have to have some idea why, Tomaki.
Did you do something bad to her? It wouldn't be the first time you did something dumb.
What are you...
Whoa, no. I didn't do anything wrong, okay? We're cool.
Are you sure?
Because the look on your face says the exact opposite of the words coming out of your mouth.
Stop reading into it. It's nothing. Leave me alone.
Come to think of it, I did see Nymph flying toward the forest last night.
At the time, it didn't seem that odd.
You mean it?
But now that I think back, she might have been fretting over something. Or I could be wrong.
Well, maybe we should go out and look for her, don't you think?
She can't miss our Christmas party tonight.
I'm not worried about it. She came back last time she did this.
Let's just focus on setting up the party. We'll wait for her if we have to.
Then how about we go find a tree for this shindig? It's one of the big things we're missing.
And speaking of big, I have to say I am partial to the large ones.
You got any idea where we can find a big one?
I actually know of an excellent spot to look.
There's an ideal tree near the riverbed next to my place.
That's great. But do you have something to chop it down with?
I'm just saying if you don't, you could always borrow my axe.
No problem there. I have the perfect axe for chopping wood.
I'll leave the rest of this to you.
See you in a little bit.
That's amazing. You're fast.
No, wait! Stop!
Icarus, you're whipping too fast now! You have to stop it!
Alright.
Oh, man.
You charred the bowl.
I have failed.
Oh, no worries. We're still having fun, right?
Just us girls making a cake together, finally having some bonding time?
I just wish Nymph could be here to enjoy it all with us.
What is that?
Oh, yeah. I brought it thinking we could use some of these pictures to decorate for the party.
Brings back some fun memories, huh?
We've done so much in the short amount of time we've known each other.
Yeah, but this one right here is my favorite of the bunch.
When we first met, I never imagined you and I would hit it off as well as we have.
But I'm glad we did.
Perfect. Seems the information you gave us was accurate. This is an excellent location. No place for her to hide. And we've got a great vantage point.
We shall be proceeding as planned.
Starting from here on out, we're going to need you to hide us with your P-Stone system. That's our best angle of attack. Don't worry. When you need help, we'll back you up.
Back me up?
That's right. With our super hot compressed projectile cannon, Prometheus. It fires vaporized matter heated to 3,000 degrees Celsius at 4 kilometers a second.
If she doesn't have the time to deploy Aegis, the Uranus Queen will be no different than any of us in a battle. We'll get her in one shot.
Hold on! I thought the orders Master gave her for the two of you to bring her back in one piece, not destroy her! In fact, I thought you were supposed to tug her into returning!
Well, that's true. But we do have to protect ourselves if things don't go according to plan. Still gotta cover our asses, don't we?
We need you to do everything you can to keep us from having to use these dangerous toys.
It'll be fine. I'm sure you'll be able to do a great job convincing her. This is just insurance.
All that we do here is for our Master. If you succeed, he will have great cause to rejoice. Don't you think?
Master will be happy with me then. I understand. But promise me you won't interfere until I finish trying to persuade her.
Oh, sure. Of course we won't.
I can't help but wonder what your true Master would think if you learned what you were doing here.
Little Miss Weapon of DEATH!
What? What are you doing?
Look, Nymph. The sky here is so vast.
It's true. Angeloids aren't designed to smile. Not unless we have humans around to help us learn.
This cage is like our chokers. If that's true, they want out.
They want out.
Hey, where are you going?
I just need to go get something I forgot.
Why don't you just give Tomaki a call? He's already out picking up things for the party.
Oh, no. I'll just...
Icarus, remember you promised you wouldn't lie anymore. You don't have to.
You're surrounded by your friends here. You can talk to us about anything. You know that, don't you?
Anyway, the cake will be out of the oven soon. So, hurry back.
Hurry back.
Icarus, what you doing? Did you come down here to pick me up?
Icarus, what you doing?
Did you come down here to pick me up?
Awesome, perfect timing.
You can help me carry one of these bags.
I got a whole bunch of stuff.
Party poppers, tinsel, way more than we need.
Master?
Oh, wait, you're gonna freak.
Check this out.
Isn't this hilarious?
Stupid, creepy Santa mask.
Master.
Come on, you gotta try it on.
Just for a sec.
That looks kick-ass.
Goodbye.
I've come to tell you goodbye.
I know our time together was short.
And I apologize for all the trouble I've caused you.
But Master?
Master?
I will never forget you.
I promise.
These memories...
I'm going to keep them forever.
Wait, what the hell?
Is this your attempt at making a joke?
Look, Icarus...
I love you, Master.
And I always have over...
Goodbye.
TARGEOUS
That had to have been caused by some kind of attack from the sky.
Beginning data scan of the impact crater.
Analysis indicates Interceptor-class Angeloids, type Gamma and type Harpy.
That's Nymph signal.
But most likely I am your target.
I will have to fight them, as the Weapon Master hates so much.
I can't go back to him anymore.
I won't ever see him again.
Goodbye? That's crap.
Wow, it's huge!
We couldn't find the perfect tree, so we settled on this one.
Mikiko's heart was set on a big tree, so that's precisely what we got.
Is Icarus here?
Tomo!
Guys!
Wait, Tomo! Where are you going?
First Icarus and Nymph show up out of nowhere, and then they just vanish.
Did they even consider the fact that I might be worried about them?
That's why I didn't want to live with them.
Because I knew I'd get attached.
If they're gone, I guess at least I'd get my peace and quiet back.
I mean, that's all I ever really wanted, right?
That's why I didn't want to live with them.
I'm sorry, Alpha, but I had to get you along for a minute to talk.
I've kept quiet about it since I showed up.
But the real reason I'm here is to take you back to the sky, of course.
Okay, then.
So, you've known?
Why am I even looking for them?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Tomoki.
Sugata, why are you here?
You're looking for Icarus and Nymph, aren't you?
According to the eyewitness reports I've gathered from the area,
she shouldn't have gone too far from here.
Judging by her direction, airspeed, and abilities,
I think it'd be best if we were to search this area here.
But if so...
I know exactly what's going through that brain of yours.
Hop on. I'll give you a pump.
That's not exactly fair.
You're running off to do all the cool stuff without me.
Why?
I said why!
What are you doing?
You said you'd let me try to convince her.
Why did you just attack her out of nowhere?
Huh.
You're such an idiot.
We lied.
Idiot or not, she helped us do this without much effort.
Good point.
Guess we should say thanks, Nymph.
We've got a lot on our plate.
Appreciate the shortcut.
What are you talking about?
What about Master?
We're here for one thing.
We need to collect her Uranus System Core,
the Variable Wings.
Master asked us to bring that back.
And only that.
Thanks for taking time to play with us, Nymph.
But you told me...
And now we're finished with you.
Get lost.
Please, don't do this.
Yeah, this was just way too easy.
Bye-bye, Uranus Queen.
Stop it!
Tomuki would never get over this.
No, I want you to stay here.
Not gonna happen.
I'm going with you.
You can't.
We're going to...
And there's a Nymph for my friends too.
It doesn't matter if you like it or not.
If you don't take me with you,
I'll karate chop you.
And I won't stop till you're dead.
Zahara.
You got ruined.
You're in pieces.
Nymph.
Hey, what's with the banners?
They were Zahara's idea.
Let's see.
Happy birthday, Icarus and Nymph?
Do Angeloids even have birthdays?
I don't know.
I asked them and they said they didn't.
So I talked about it with Sugata and Prez
and we decided to give them one.
I suppose it makes sense for Christmas
to be the birthday for angels.
Why are you doing all this?
Well, Icarus is still so...
I don't know.
She's like a porcelain doll or something.
Never smiling or anything.
And Nymph tries to hide it,
but it's obvious she feels lonely.
So we decided to take today's Christmas party
and make it their birthday party too.
Thought it might cheer them up.
Oh, and Tomaki, look at this.
Ta-da!
A photo album I made with all the stuff
we've done together.
Wow, this takes me back.
It's from our camping trip ride.
And this one's from our day at the beach.
I look great.
They have pictures from the cultural festival too.
Here, look.
These are really nice shots.
And I'm sure Icarus and Nymph will smile
without even thinking about it
when they set their eyes on these.
I hope so.
I had no idea what to get for them,
so I thought this would at least be a nice gesture.
What's wrong, Tomaki?
You don't look too keen about all this.
You do want to do something nice for them, right?
Something to give them a reason to truly smile.
I don't think I can.
All I was ever good at was making them cry.
I've sure never made either one of them smile before.
You're like Sahara.
Huh?
Even if you can't help,
there must be something you can do.
Something only you can do.
That is, if you don't want to regret everything forever.
I wonder what kind of presents they would like.
There's got to be something I could buy
that would make them happy.
No way!
You took a direct hit from the Prometheus.
How are you even standing?
I sure don't know.
Why don't you try asking the two of them directly?
Yeah, I think that's what I'm going to do.
But first we've got to bring them home.
This...
This is terrible.
Nymph's wings, they were beautiful.
What happened here?
Variable wing system, safeties removed.
Alpha, stop!
Double kill, find out!
You can't!
Activate mode Uranus Queen.
Now.
Alpha!
Master.
I'm so sorry.
I have been lying to you from the beginning.
I am a strategic battle-class Angeloid,
type Alpha, Icarus.
I'm the weapon you hate so very much.
Yeah, I know.
Icarus, listen.
When I told you I didn't want you to be a weapon,
it's because I felt bad for you.
What?
You adopted a watermelon
and started raising baby chicks.
You have such a kind heart.
The idea that you were created to be a killing machine
was just too much.
I didn't want that for you.
Thank you.
But you know,
I'll tell you how I'm looking at it right now.
Right now, I am more than happy you're a weapon.
Because now you can save our friend.
Yes.
My master.
Icarus, you have to save Nymph.
Kick their ass.
I'm type Alpha, Icarus.
You can do it.
Engage targets.
Dammit, she's coming.
Split up.
Right.
Come on, let's use this chance to break Nymph's chain.
Nymph, are you okay?
She doesn't look good.
Screw this.
I'm sure she has some loser for a master anyway.
No!
You don't know what might happen!
You bitch!
Die!
Oh!
Honey.
Now hold still.
Igis.
Just fight through it!
Connect.
No, that's the Uranus... system!
Circeus.
Dammit! You can't cut it like that! My joker's a bomb! Once the time limit is up, they'll send an ignition code to blow it up! If you cut off the chain before then, it might explode!
We might be able to cut through a part that's been twisted with this axe handle.
Yeah, let's try it.
Would you people listen to what I'm saying? Everyone in this entire area could be killed! It could blow us all into oblivion!
Yeah, so what about it?
If you hadn't figured it out yet, we're your friends, Nymph.
And when friends are in trouble, you help them. We're just doing what comes naturally.
Why... Alpha... I don't understand... any of this.
We Angeloids have never thought about happiness since our inception. This is just how we were created. We exist for the sole purpose of making our masters happy.
But now... all of these feelings I've been having... they're so new...
I'm not sure... but I think... I might feel happy right now...
Perhaps... this is true happiness I'm experiencing... Alpha? Am I right? Is this it?
Is this it?
Because for the first time... I'm really smiling...
I'm crying!
.
Full retreat of enemy combatants, confirmed! Disengage uranous queen mode.
StarTalks
Yo, Pinkarus...
Check it out!
I'm so glad.
It's going to be a white Christmas.
It's beautiful.
I see now.
The sky from down here, it is like heaven.
You can see the溢れ of학.
The sky from grade 10 or r uwagę wouldn't be perfect for me.
二人重ねた季節 壊さすぎ
ただ怖がってた 未来の訪れさえ
あなたと並んでる 今なら待ち遠しい
こんな気持ち あなたに 届けてもいいのかな
そばにいられるだけで うれしくなる
変わりゆく空の下 私も変わりたいの
いつかあなたのように そっと笑えたら
memory christmas!
and happy birthday!
także、ニフ
あれはどう言 could You two
All right, you two. I got something to say. I want you to stay here for as long as you like. So, yeah. Think of it as my birthday-slash-Christmas present to you both. And here. A little something extra.
Tomo! You're always pulling this cheap-ass crap just like you did with me!
Well, what do you know? Nice job, Alpha.
Holy crap! You just laughed a little bit, didn't you? Do it again. Try doing it one more time.
Laughing.
You dingbat!
It's about 20 MPs.
All right, I can do it.
I'm getting ready.
You hiccuping 2 solarets around.
You wait ...
You wouldn't even have aips!